<ORGANIZATION>:
Name: <PERSON>
Date of Birth: <DATE_TIME>Address: <DATE_TIME> Oak Street, <LOCATION>, <LOCATION>, NY <DATE_TIME>
Phone: <PHONE_NUMBER>
Email: <EMAIL_ADDRESS>
Emergency Contact: <PERSON>, <PHONE_NUMBER>

Medical Record Number: MR-<PHONE_NUMBER>
Insurance: Blue Cross Blue Shield, Policy #BCBS-<US_DRIVER_LICENSE>-01
Group Number: <DATE_TIME>

Chief Complaint:
Patient presents with persistent chest pain and shortness of breath for <DATE_TIME>.

History of Present Illness:
Ms. <PERSON> is a <DATE_TIME> female with no significant past medical history who began experiencing intermittent chest pain <DATE_TIME>. The pain is described as pressure-like, radiating to the left arm and jaw. Associated symptoms include shortness of breath, fatigue, and occasional dizziness. Pain is exacerbated by physical activity and relieved with rest.

- Hypertension (diagnosed <DATE_TIME>)
- Seasonal allergies
- No previous surgeries

Current Medications:
- Lisinopril 10mg <DATE_TIME>
- Claritin 10mg as needed

Physical Examination:
Vital Signs:
- Blood Pressure: 145/95 mmHg
- Heart Rate: 88 bpm
- Respiratory Rate: 18/min
- Temperature: 98.6°F
Abdomen: Soft, non-tender, non-distended

<NRP> Tests:
<ORGANIZATION>: Normal sinus rhythm, no acute changes
Chest X-ray: Normal cardiac silhouette, clear lung fields
Troponin: 0.02 ng/mL (normal <0.04)
<PERSON> Count: WBC 7.2, <PERSON>, Plt 245

Assessment:
1. Atypical chest pain, likely musculoskeletal in origin
2. Hypertension, uncontrolled
3. Rule out coronary artery disease

Plan:
1. Schedule stress test within <DATE_TIME>
2. Increase Lisinopril to 20mg <DATE_TIME>
3. Follow up in <DATE_TIME>
4. Return to emergency department if chest pain worsens or new symptoms develop

Prescribed Medications:
- Lisinopril 20mg tablet, 1 tablet <DATE_TIME>
- Nitroglycerin 0.4mg sublingual tablets, 1 tablet as needed for chest pain

Dietary Recommendations:
- Low sodium diet (<2000mg <DATE_TIME>)
- Heart-healthy diet with emphasis on fruits, vegetables, and lean proteins

Activity Restrictions:
- Avoid heavy lifting and strenuous exercise until stress test completed
- Walking and light activities permitted

Appointment scheduled for <DATE_TIME> at <DATE_TIME> with Dr. <PERSON>

Physician: Dr. <PERSON>, <LOCATION>
License Number: NY-<US_DRIVER_LICENSE>
Date: <DATE_TIME>

This report contains confidential patient information protected by HIPAA regulations.
